Now this is mostly review I just want to make sure we're very clear on hypotheticals so that we understand
现在这主要是评论，我只是想确保我们对假设非常清楚，以便我们理解
the basic grammar structure so that you're able to use it for the next part.
基本语法结构，以便您能够在下一部分中使用它。
When we talk about possibilities.
当我们谈论可能性时。
So just as a review a hypothetical is something that we imagine that is not true and may never be true
因此，就像评论一样，假设是我们想象的不真实的东西，可能永远不会是真实的
if monkeys could fly if monkeys could fly.
如果猴子会飞，如果猴子会飞。
They would rule the earth.
他们将统治地球。
OK so we can just imagine anything that way.
好的，所以我们可以这样想象任何事情。
If people lived on Mars then I would go there.
如果人们住在火星上，那么我会去那里。
We can talk about our actions if another thing happens.
如果发生另一件事，我们可以谈论我们的行为。
That's what you would do but it may never happen.
这就是你会做的，但它可能永远不会发生。
OK if would if I would if I lived in Beijing.
好吧，如果我住在北京的话。
Notice that we use the past tense here and we're using past tense even though it's not really in the
请注意，我们在这里使用了过去时，并且我们使用的是过去时，即使它不是真的在
past is it.
过去了。
No.
不。
If I lived in Beijing I would never take the subway.
如果我住在北京，我永远不会坐地铁。
Could we say I would never take the subway if I lived in Beijing.
如果我住在北京，我们能不能说我永远不会坐地铁。
The answer is yes.
答案是肯定的。
But just as before we would take out that comma OK same thing.
但是就像以前一样，我们会去掉那个逗号 OK 一样的东西。
If I were a doctor I would charge less.
如果我是医生，我会收取更少的费用。
So maybe I think doctors charge too much money.
所以也许我认为医生收费太高了。
I can say that because I'm not a doctor and I probably never will be.
我可以这么说是因为我不是医生，而且我可能永远也不会。
In fact I'm pretty sure I won't be but if I were.
事实上，我很确定我不会，但如果我是的话。
Now notice we use were here if you were if she was if he was if we were we use this to create hypothetical
现在请注意，如果你在，如果她在，如果他在，如果我们在，我们会在这里使用
use if then we say I would she would they would would is very important here.
使用 if then we say I would she would they would 在这里非常重要。
It tells us that it isn't real.
它告诉我们它不是真实的。
It tells us that we are just imagining it.
它告诉我们，我们只是在想象它。
These are a little bit different because lived in the past tense but actually they're very similar because
这些有点不同，因为它们是过去式，但实际上它们非常相似，因为
I don't live in Beijing and may never I'm not a doctor and may never be.
我不住在北京，可能永远不会我不是医生，也可能永远不会。
So this has to be very very clear because this is so common in English.
所以这必须非常非常清楚，因为这在英语中很常见。
It's very important that you really understand how to use this type of sentence so we know how to talk
您真正了解如何使用此类句子非常重要，因此我们知道如何说话
about our intentions and our actions.
关于我们的意图和行动。
The cause of the result which is what we do and we know how to talk about hypotheticals things we imagine
结果的原因是我们所做的，我们知道如何谈论我们想象的假设事物
so let's kind of bring all this together and talk about back to our topic.
所以让我们把所有这些放在一起，回到我们的话题。
Future Possibilities things that may or may not happen often these are things that are out of our control
未来的可能性 可能会或可能不会经常发生的事情 这些是我们无法控制的事情
or we could also often say out of our hands it's out of your hands that means you have no control over
或者我们也可以经常说失控，这意味着你无法控制
some part of it but if you have no control over some thing that may or may not happen in the future
它的某些部分，但是如果您无法控制将来可能发生或可能不会发生的某些事情
you can talk about actions that you will do.
你可以谈论你将要采取的行动。
If this happens or if this happens you can talk about actions that will happen whether or not this happens.
如果发生这种情况或发生这种情况，您可以谈论无论这种情况发生与否都会发生的行动。
So that might be a little bit difficult to understand but let me explain.
所以这可能有点难以理解，但让我解释一下。
OK.
好的。
OK it may rain tomorrow it may not.
好吧，明天可能会下雨，但可能不会。
If it doesn't rain tomorrow I guess we can go to the zoo.
如果明天不下雨，我想我们可以去动物园。
So maybe a father is speaking to his children.
所以也许一位父亲正在对他的孩子们说话。
Children say Can we go to the zoo tomorrow.
孩子们说我们明天可以去动物园吗？
Well if it doesn't rain tomorrow I guess means that's OK I guess we can go to the zoo.
好吧，如果明天不下雨，我想就意味着没关系，我想我们可以去动物园。
If it does rain tomorrow will we go to the zoo.
如果明天下雨，我们就去动物园。
No no we will not.
不，不，我们不会。
OK.
好的。
If I go to Canada next year I will stay in Toronto.
如果我明年去加拿大，我会留在多伦多。
Now maybe I have some control over whether or not I go to Canada.
现在也许我可以控制是否去加拿大。
We don't know all of the details in that situation.
我们不知道那种情况下的所有细节。
If I go where will I stay.
如果我去，我会留在哪里。
TORONTO If I don't go I won't go to Toronto.
多伦多 如果我不去，我就不会去多伦多。
But I have the next action sort of ready.
但我已经准备好下一步行动了。
I have the next plan ready for if this thing does happen and it may or may not.
我已经准备好下一个计划，如果这件事真的发生了，它可能会也可能不会。
If my English improves I should be able to get that accounting job so maybe this course is helping you
如果我的英语提高了，我应该能够得到那份会计工作，所以也许这门课程对你有帮助
improve your English and there are many other things you can do to improve your English if your English
提高你的英语水平，如果你的英语水平，你可以做很多其他的事情来提高你的英语水平
improves.
改善。
What will happen if my English improves I can get that accounting job.
如果我的英语提高了我能得到那份会计工作会发生什么。
You have this job you really really want to be an accountant maybe in an international company.
你有这份工作，你真的很想成为一名会计师，也许是在一家国际公司。
And the result.
和结果。
That thing that you want.
你想要的东西。
It depends on whether or not your English gets better.
这取决于你的英语是否变得更好。
If it doesn't well you get the job.
如果做得不好，你就会得到这份工作。
No.
不。
If my English doesn't improve well then I guess I'll just stay at my current job.
如果我的英语没有提高，那么我想我会继续我现在的工作。
So again we have two possibilities because we really don't know what's going to happen here.
所以我们有两种可能性，因为我们真的不知道这里会发生什么。
We can plan for the future this way.
我们可以这样规划未来。
This is how we talk about alternatives alternatives.
这就是我们谈论替代品的方式。
An alternative is another choice.
另一种选择是另一种选择。
You could do this or this or this or this and this is the grammar that we used to do that.
你可以做这个或这个或这个或这个，这是我们过去做的语法。
This is how we express it.
这就是我们表达它的方式。